No Escaping The End of the World
Mega Cyclone is a tv movie, science fiction, action
film directed by Sheldon Wilson.
Jupiter’s famous blemish, the Great Red Spot, has vanished.
When massive storms are reported in North America, it quickly becomes apparent that the huge, high
storm that has been swirling around Jupiter for hundreds of years has landed on Earth.
Swallowing up everything in its path, the Great Red Spot threatens to transform
Earth into another Jupiter-like gas giant in just a matter of days!
aka Mega Cyclone
Jason Newmar, played by David Sutcliffe.
Gunter MacGregor, played by Mitch Pileggi.
Will Newmar, played by Brett Dier.
Andrea Newmar, played by Leah Cairns.
Megan MacGregor, played by Luisa d'Oliveira.
Carolyn, played by Erica Cerra.
Cindy Busby (born March 18, 1983) is a Canadian actress and singer.
She portrayed Ashley Stanton on Heartland, and has played many
roles in Hallmark movies, including Marrying Mr.
Darcy, Follow Me to Daisy Hills, and Warming Up to You.
The film explores themes of jupiter, hurricane, disaster, storm.
The tone is thought_provoking.